{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_9_3KXVYX",
                "player_11_3KXVYX",
                "player_15_3KXVYX",
                "player_3_3KXVYX",
                "player_10_3KXVYX",
                "player_5_3KXVYX"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                9,
                11,
                15,
                3,
                10,
                5
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "liedown",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone.",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    804.914,
                    8851.828,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    -121.12167694173395,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    760.806,
                    9217.939,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    10.966154282889988,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    815.303,
                    8670.63,
                    1248.15,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    702.078,
                    8647.76,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    105.03592248601069,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    270.255,
                    8502.066,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    -163.1288022915945,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    419.303,
                    8721.503,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    164.325261922278,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            1423.585,
            7934.963,
            1537.92
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1672.844211828597
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            464.462,
            7877.118,
            1538.151,
            0,
            79.93865066682211,
            0
        ],
        [
            1354.989,
            8884.763,
            1259.711,
            0,
            -170.20799230016706,
            0
        ],
        [
            1124.479,
            8042.187,
            1248.15,
            0,
            125.13205643265988,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "six"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many people are in a crouch position in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are male?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many men who are not bald are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many individuals are neither bald nor wearing glasses in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in the brown sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "C. holding something"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. stand"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the burgundy polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. jumping",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the_man_in_white_shirt relative to the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants relative to the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the_woman_in_camo_vest relative to the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants relative to the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. In front of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the_man_in_blue_polo relative to the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. In front of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants relative to the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the back-left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-left of"
            }
        }
    }
}